(Howard:)Me too.
(Howard:)But probably in a different way.
She's really hooked on "Age of Conan."
She's playing non-stop.
Oh, yes, online gaming addiction.
(Raj:)There's nothing worse than having
that multiplayer monkey on your back.
- Sheldon, wake up.
- Danger, danger.
(Leslie(arriving):)Afternoon, men. Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Oh, yeah, well, your attempt
at juvenilizing me...
(Sheldon:)...by excluding me from the set of adult
males just... Oh, I'm too tired to do this.
(Leslie:)Right. I heard you've been pulling
all-nighters with Middle-Earth Barbie.
(Sheldon:)She comes into my room.
No one's supposed to be in my room.
(Leslie:)I would postulate
she's escaping into the online world...
(Leslie:)...to compensate
for her sexual frustration.
(Howard:)I do that too.
(Howard:)But probably in a different way.